farespotter.net 2018-06-11

# Privacy Policy

At MediaAlpha, protecting your personal information is a top priority. This Privacy Policy provides details on how we treat your personal information. QuoteLab, LLC, which does business as MediaAlpha ("we" or “us”), is the Data Controller with respect to information collected on the websites we own.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to:

  * information collected through this website, FareSpotter.net, along with any other website owned and operated by MediaAlpha (the “Sites”);
  * information you enter into our forms appearing on third-party websites;
  * certain limited information regarding your interaction with advertiser sites following a visit to our Sites, solely for attribution and optimization purposes;
  * information obtained during phone calls to us that you initiate, or that we or our partners may initiate with your prior consent; and
  * any other information you choose to provide to us.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or to which we may link (except for the limited situation set forth above), or to any information you may provide directly to an insurance agent or carrier, travel agent, or other service provider who you are connected with through our service.

#### Information We Collect and Use

We collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through the Sites. Specifically, we collect information provided by you in connection with obtaining price quotes or rates. For example, you may be asked to provide your name, address, telephone number, email, and other information in order to be matched to insurance carriers and agents who may provide you a quote for their insurance services. Or you may be asked to provide home and destination airports and travel dates so that we can show you flight and hotel options.

We may also collect other information such as gender, zip code, or other demographic information that is not tied to your personal information. Included in this demographic information is your IP address, which is treated as personal information in some jurisdictions, but which we use only to identify your geographic area and for legal compliance purposes.

In addition, we might receive information about you from other online or offline sources and may combine that information with the information you have provided.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We share personal information about you under the following circumstances:

Quote Requests. If you submit a request for price quotes for insurance products or other products or services, we will share the personal information contained in your request form (such as your name, address, telephone number, email, information about your cars, travel destination, etc.) with third parties, which may include agents, carriers, lead aggregators, and other service providers in our network, to process and fulfill your request.

Our agreements require service providers to secure any personal information we provide to them and limit how they can use such information. Our agreements also require these service providers to comply with national, state and other applicable privacy regulations. By submitting your request to us, you understand that service providers may contact you by telephone (including through automated calling or using recorded messages), email, or regular mail based on the information you provided to us, in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, or any similar mechanism to opt-out of receiving phone calls or email messages.

If one of the service providers contacts you and you wish not to be contacted again by that service provider, then you should specifically make a request of them. Please note that service providers may maintain the information you provided whether or not you elect to use their services.

Aggregate, Non-Personal, or De-identified Information. We may share aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) and other non-personal, de-identified, or anonymous information we collect, with third parties to optimize their ability to reach their target markets.

As Required by Law. We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances whenever we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

Business Transfer. As with any other business, it is possible that we could in the future enter into a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale. If such a transaction occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by us, including your personal information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

#### Information Collection Technologies

To better serve our users and service providers and to analyze and enhance the performance of our Sites, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about our users, such as your browsing behavior, links clicked, device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Sites and our advertisers.

To opt-out of the use of cookies on our Sites, you can change your browser options to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Certain aspects of our service may be limited if you do not accept cookies. More information about cookies and other tracking technologies is available at allaboutcookies.org or youronlinechoices.eu.To opt-out of the use of cookies on our Sites, you can change your browser options to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Certain aspects of our service may be limited if you do not accept cookies. More information about cookies and other tracking technologies is available at allaboutcookies.org or youronlinechoices.eu.

Special Note for European Visitors. In connection with the effectiveness of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Economic Area (EEA), MediaAlpha has determined to eliminate or limit the use of cookies and similar technologies with visitors from the EEA. Specifically:

  * If you visit a third-party site that uses our services, we will not place any cookies on your device.
  * We will not seek your consent to use cookies in this instance, though the publisher of the site may do so.
  * If you visit one of or our owned and operated sites, we will only place limited third-party cookies, such as those made available for analytics purposes by Google and Bing.
  * In this case, we will seek your consent to use these third-party cookies and will only do so after you indicate your consent. If you do not consent, then no cookies will be written to your device.

To enable this feature, we use third-party tools to determine your geographic location; if these tools indicate that you are in the EEA, then we treat your visit as above. If you feel that you are subject to the GDPR, but we have nonetheless used cookies in connection with your visit without consent - which may be due to a failure of the third party geolocation tools; your use of a proxy server, your location outside of the EEA at the time of your visit; or some other factor beyond our control – please notify us at [dpo@mediaalpha.com](mailto:dpo@mediaalpha.com) with any relevant details so that we can ensure proper treatment of your data under GDPR. 

#### Emails

By providing your contact information to us, you are registering to receive communications from us directly or through a third-party. If you provide your e-mail address and request to be added to any of our travel deal or other mailing lists, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails with offers and promotions. Our emails will always identify MediaAlpha or one of our branded sites as the sender. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to Customer Care at [info@mediaalpha.com](mailto:info@mediaalpha.com). You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails.

#### Third-Party Advertisers

Please note that we only control our own mailing list and policies. Third-party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services. In addition, if you provide your personal information to a service provider in our network, any use of your information by that service provider will be subject to their privacy policies and procedures. You would need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications.

#### Confidentiality and Security

The security of your personal information is very important, and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example, we limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who need the information to provide requested products and services to you. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with or exceed federal standards to guard your personal information, and we anonymize or expunge data when it is no longer necessary to provide services to our users or substantiate records for our partners.

#### Third-Party Links

This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to us. However, when you visit links from our Sites, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third-party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain services through a third-party site, the data collected by the third-party is governed by their privacy policy. A third-party site should also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and other tracking technologies. We encourage you to review the policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

#### A Special Note about Children's Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our websites only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.

#### Updating, Obtaining or Removing Your Information

Upon request via email or mail, we will provide you a summary of personal information retained by us. We will only send your personal records to your email address or postal address that we have on file for you. To obtain, modify, correct, change, update or remove your personal records from our database, please send your request via email to our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@mediaalpha.com](mailto:dpo@mediaalpha.com). We will require that you prove your identity before providing any personal information.

#### Special Notice to California Residents

California residents may, no more than once per calendar year, request information about our disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To be valid, requests must be submitted to us at dpo@mediaalpha.com. Within thirty days of receiving this request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed for direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of the third parties.

#### Visitors outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our Sites from residents of the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By visiting our Sites or using our services, you acknowledge and agree that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy, regardless of the laws of your residence country.

To the extent the laws of another jurisdiction apply to your data or use of the Sites, we will comply with such laws.

#### Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending an email to: [info@mediaalpha.com](mailto:info@mediaalpha.com).

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will prominently post notice of such changes on the Sites. However, you should check this Privacy Policy whenever you use any of our Sites to ensure you are aware of our current privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our Sites after we have posted any changes indicates your agreement to the changes, unless you notify us otherwise.

#### Your Agreement

By using this Site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any portion of our Sites.

Updated May 2018
